

TypeScript, Angular, SaSS, NGRX

PROFILE

Developer with two years of experiences in Web development.

Passionate about creating and understanding the dynamics of the technology market, Master in Business Digital Strategy.

I am looking for a place where I can combine my programming skills with my experience from the social sciences to improve the products that the client receives.

CONTACT

Phone +55 (12) 936180526

Email radapls8@gmail.com

Website radapls.github.com

in LinkedIn www.linkedin.com/in/radapls

Location São José dos Campos or Remote

LANGUAGES

Spanish - Native English - Intermediate Portuguese - Intermediate

HOBBIES

Cooking Sewina AR filters

TOOLS

















EXPERIENCE

January 2022 - Present

Frontend Developer, Wiboo Company 👩

Creation of functionalities, maintenance of the state of the web and mobile code. Management of Planner under the Scrum Agile model for the follow-up of tasks and deliverables. Development tools: TypeScript / NativeScript, Angular, Saas, NGRX. HTTP requests.

July 2020 - December 2021

Social Researcher, Instituto de Estudios Interculturales



March 2019 - December 2019

Devlovery Unit Member, Secretaria de Gobierno, Alcaldia Municipal de Santiago de Cali.

January - June 2018

Research Assistant. Misión de Observación Electoral

March - June 2017 Research Instructor, Carrera de Ciencia Política, Pontificia Universidad

August - November 2016

Research Instructor, Instituto de Estudios Interculturales



EDUCATION

2021-2022

Universidad ICESI - Master in Digital Business Strategy Emphasis on prototyping and user validation on the different projects. Creation of the SIGET-RB for the management of Telepacfico transportation.

2014-2019

Pontificia Universidad Javeriana Cali - Political Scientist Creation of two research seedbeds. Development of design skills